We are about to start our live broadcast.
Are you ready?
Let me introduce myself first. I am Tina from CLOUD.
Today I am here to introduce how to make a live show in CLOUD.
Today is not Ms. Moni. Today is the first time Ms. Tina is here for a live broadcast.
If you are here, you can send some comments.
Let's see how many people are here.
Thank you all for coming.
Let's start today's course.
First, let's open the CLOUD app.
Let me introduce you first.
In this live broadcast,
there are three sections.
The first section is to introduce how to make a live show basic operation.
You can see that it is a very basic model.
The second section will introduce how to make a live show with a multi-layer structure.
Then, we will see the third section.
It will introduce how to make a live show with a head or hat,
earrings,
belt,
and metal ring.
I will introduce how to make a live show with these details in the clothes.
In addition, I will introduce how to use CLOUD stage.
and how to use the Cloth stage.
First of all, let's go into the first part.
Here, I will open the basic style file first.
After this outfit comes in,
you can see that this style is actually very simple.
It's just two pieces together.
And then,
this style,
we may go straight to the show in a normal situation.
When you go to the show,
there are actually some little tricks before you start.
For example, when we finish our normal clothes,
it's a high-quality state.
What does that mean?
That is, the size of our board will usually be set to 5,
and the thickness will be set to 1.
Then the model's surface diameter is set to 0.
For this value,
we usually use this tool to do it.
So basically it's 510.
But you need to know that in such a high-quality state,
the simulation speed of our clothing is very slow.
In this case,
if I go straight to the show,
it's not good for me to check if there are any unstable problems in the show.
So, before you get ready to record the show,
is it quiet now?
We just closed the window.
Then, before you record the show,
you need to check it first.
Make some adjustments.
We first need to lift the sheet of the sheet.
Give it to him first.
Like this dress,
it's a big piece.
You can just give it to him to 20.
If there are some small details on your clothing,
you can make it a little smaller than 20.
Then, including the show,
we know that the board and the board will collide in the process of dynamic.
There is a conflict.
So in order to prevent multiple layers of clothing from colliding with each other,
and then penetrating,
we need to increase the thickness of this conflict a little bit before the show.
Here, I give him the default setting of 2.5.
Then, the model's surface diameter,
it's okay.
Because usually when we walk,
we will be more distant.
Of course, if you want to adjust it to 0,
it's okay.
But you need to know.
If it's set to 0,
my model's skin will come out.
Because our example is set to 20.
I'll give him a little bit of it here.
OK, for this ordinary one,
we know that it's like this.
The fabric of his clothing is very soft.
It's very soft.
It's easy to stretch
So it leads to a very large over-stretching of this large collar
We can check the length of the collar line
You can see that the difference between the 2D and 3D lines is very large
If we go for a walk in this case
There will be some problems
If we have experienced students, we may know
In this state, if we walk directly
The collar may fall down
So I'll give you this first
Because I'm here on the main menu
We have chosen the animation mode in the upper right corner of the main interface
Let me introduce you to the basic interface of animation first
Then I will show you later
What happens if you walk directly
First of all, after we come to this interface
Let's do it again
After coming to this interface
There should be a spring warning
Will say
When you need to walk
You need to adjust the quality of the simulation to complete
This is the animation state
I'll adjust it manually here
What does it mean
Our normal default speed simulation
It is more suitable for making clothing
Because of its simulation
You can see that the number of simulations here is 1
So its simulation speed is very fast
We know that clothing is in the process of dynamic
Because there is this kind of collision between each other
So we can switch it to
A animation completion
In this case, its simulation will increase from 1 to 5
That is to say
I will simulate the same dynamic action five times
In this way, the result of the simulation will be more accurate
So this also means that its calculation will increase
So we use a completed simulation
Its simulation speed will be much lower than the normal simulation
This is inevitable
But to ensure the simulation of this one is guaranteed
The simulation simulation is stable
It must be switched to this completion
Then let's take a look again
Now below this is our animation editor
Then we see below
Now here
There are some buttons here
Wait a minute
Look here first
Here are some of our progress bars
First of all, this is a default one
I was in a default state of the pose before
I'll adjust it to the far right
First of all
We are now going to add a model action
In the library
We have found the model in the preset folder
Because I am a model of V2
So you have to open the V2 folder
Then find a motion folder in it
Then there will be some related action files in it
It should be noted that we are now using version 5.2
In the version before 5.2
We only have the model of V1
There is a motion
This is version 5.1
Only version V1 has a motion
So after we got to V2
After we got to 5.2
V1 and V2 all have a motion
After we found it here
We first double-click to import an action
Let's talk about this window
That is to say
It will move the costume and the model to the starting position of the action
We'll find out later
Then we see that it will have a transition into the first position of the action
We can hook it up and click OK first
See the model from the center of the coordinate
Move to the right back of the space
It's because it's going to walk out of a path like this
Walk out and walk back
Let's talk about this again
This is to move the model and the virtual model costume to the starting position
Just move here
There was also a position called the first position of the transition into the action
Now we just hooked it up
So you can see that there is an action bar here
What is this action bar
Let's pull this progress bar
You can see that it has a transition action
It's a little slow
It's too late to memorize the notes, isn't it?
It's okay, you can remember the focus
I talk a lot
You can pull the progress bar here
Then pull the screen further
In the process of pulling
We can preview the model
What is the action of this model
After confirming
Let's pull it back
Be sure to return to the starting position
In this way, your model and clothes will be reunited again
If you are in this state in the middle
I just changed an action
Then your model and clothes can't go back together
It's very annoying
So go back to the starting position
This is this action
We just saw that there was a transition action here, right?
I'm changing another action
This time I put the second one
The first position of the transition action is to take it away
Re-select and click OK
At this time, you will see that this transition action is not imported
The model is a direct transition
In this way, your clothes and models are separated
This is not good for our production
So I'll cancel it here
So everyone should remember
Every time you make an action, hook up both
Then we pull it again
You can see that there are five walking movements in it
Each is different
When everyone is making a choice
You need to pay attention to whether your clothing details are suitable for this action
For example, my model is a rectangular board
So there are a lot of fabrics piled up below
At this time, if you use this posture
I can already imagine that this place may bring some instability
Because my hand will be stuck in my waist
There will be a conflict with my fabric
So this style is not suitable for this action
I'll just choose the first action here
We can also drag it to the 3D window
After entering
We can see here
There is a movement and action
This is a model action progress bar
Come in
Then talk about this row
Let's first see this button
This button is a recording button
When you turn on recording
Confirm before recording
Animation completed
When you turn on recording
Your model will start to move according to the previous progress bar
At the same time, you can see that the simulation button is open
So this is the model with clothes to simulate
At the same time
There will be a clothing progress bar below
In the slow production
At this time
The system will record the entire dynamic process of your clothing
On this progress bar
At this time
Let's wait a moment
Wait a moment
You can see later
What will happen to our clothes
What kind of problem
Now you can see
If we don't make any adjustments
It will fall down
Right
At this time, I can actually analyze
What caused it
This action bar has been discarded
We can delete it by right-clicking
Let's go back to our simulation mode
To make some adjustments to this dress
So before we go to the show
Usually it's about clothing
It's a dynamic stability of the dress
To make some adjustments
For example, here
It's obvious that the neck stretch is too big
At this time
We can select the entire line of the collar
Then in the counting calculator
Give it the elasticity
Open
Then set the ratio to 100%
The default is 80
We set it to 100%
100% means
I hope this line won't be stretched
Don't be shortened
In addition
You can also use this chainstay
It's okay to add it to the collar
Anyway, here
Two choices
It's okay
Then let's simulate
At this time
This collar will give it
Put it on
At this time
Let's adjust it a little bit
Don't let it bend
In this way
This collar won't be stretched
There is another potential problem
My collar is relatively large
In the process of walking
It may bend to the left
Or bend to the right
At this time
We'd better
Fix the position of the collar
Let it be in the process of walking
Won't run around
Run around
At this time
Can be used
A very useful tool
In our 3D tool bar
You can find it
It's called
The armor
In fact, it is a armor tool
Long press armor
There is a fixed one below
On the virtual model
It means
Put this
A point on the costume
And a point on the model
Fix it up
The operation method
Is a single left click
Then left click
This will fix these two points
And then
Left click
This two points are fixed
Let's simulate
Just now
Our Dong Ge
Shanghai has a question
I just didn't see
He said how to operate it back to the center
Because my model is already on the side
How to get back to the center
Right click on the model
There is a function called moving virtual model clothing to the center
OK?
Doesn't the model hurt?
The model is hard
It shouldn't hurt
Let's simulate it again
Simulate to make sure these two points are fixed
After that
Next we can start to do a walk-through
Well, you can use this low-quality one first
It's already 20
Try walking first
See if there's a problem
Because the speed is faster
If there's no problem
Then we'll give it back
Just like the initial needle
Then back
Then go back to the simulation mode
To reduce its particle diameter again
But don't reduce the impact thickness anymore
The impact thickness is still there
Make it a little more stable
After the particle diameter is reduced
We'll come back and do a final recording of the action
In this way, you can save some time
Now I'll let him walk for two steps
In the process of walking
Let me see what questions you asked
Can you hear the sound of my laptop running
Can the OBJ on the clothing go to the show?
Can go to the show
The third part will be introduced later
You can listen to the sound while talking
It's not cool
I just want to listen to the sound
This software
Is there any difference between MD9?
The difference between cloud software and MD software
It's mainly about its industry
Is not the same
In the case of cloud
Mainly targeting the clothing industry
So it will be with
Our clothing version
There is a good compatibility
What we can import
Email file
At the same time 2D 1D
There are also many types of editing tools in the software.
In the case of MT, it is mainly aimed at the game animation industry.
In that software, it does not have this kind of import version.
Then there will be a lot of limitations to these editing tools for the version.
So it's not the same for this demand.
Wow, this is too much.
Watch out for safety while walking.
Ok, I'll record it here.
Because basically it has finished most of the way.
In fact, you can already see it.
Basically, there will be nothing.
What's the problem?
Right?
It's all OK.
The whole shape is OK.
It's still very upright.
At this time, you can go back to the simulation mode.
And then put this version of the particle monitor.
The particle monitor, in fact, takes a lot of time to walk.
If you want the highest quality output, you can reduce it to five.
Then go again.
Or if you think you want to maintain quality and efficiency, you want to make it faster.
But it looks better.
A little bit.
Then you can adjust it to eight or so.
Don't be less than eight.
In this way, its fold will be relatively smooth and natural.
And then the speed of the simulation recording will be relatively faster than five.
I'll simulate it a little bit.
You can see that its fold will become more delicate.
In this state, you go back to the animation mode.
Go down and walk again.
Go to the end.
You can finish this clothing walk.
The time here is off.
I'm here.
I recorded one in advance.
It's for everyone to take a look at.
What kind of configuration does Pro need to not lag?
What is Pro?
Is it Mac?
I'm done recording here.
This is finished recording.
After that, let's talk about the following settings.
First of all, this is a playback.
After we're done recording, you can click play to check your recording progress.
You can see that this speed is very slow, right?
Then we can set its playback speed next to it.
Change the speed of the needle to the speed of the needle.
Then it will be a normal one.
A walk.
That's a speed.
And then you can see that there's a loop playback here.
What's the other one?
You can see that every time you play, the model will have a turn around.
Right?
We can have a blue progress bar here.
Put the鼠不要 to put the blue progress bar on the top.
The leftmost end.
When the鼠不要 becomes a vertical line plus a left arrow.
To pull this progress bar.
Pull it to this position of this turn around.
on that
It can start to move after the sound is turned on
Then this is the button
It's back to the first point
The first point of our playback area
Blue is our playback area
And then we just let it go like this
And then when it goes back to the right
Will automatically
Turn back and go continuously
And then this side
It can set its playback speed
Then look to the right again
Look to the right again
This is relatively
What is the current point
Start and end point
Then talk about this
This is a ratio of your time axis
Now is a normal speed is 1
We can adjust the ratio of this time axis
Make a adjustment
For example, I will adjust it to 0.5
Then its speed will be faster
Then this time axis will affect you
The process of recording the movement of the walk show
Just
When will it be used
For example, we usually do it sometimes
A little bigger
At this time
For example, the style of your recording is very complicated
In the speed of 1
It's hard to stabilize it
Some of its structures are animated in a dynamic way
Then you can put its speed at this time
Give it a bigger ratio
Then let it have more simulation real numbers
In this case, it can
Stabilize those details more stably
Of course it will also consume more
It will consume more time
You can learn more about it here
Then there is a needle on the right
Or a switch of seconds
And then here is the ratio
This is the ratio of our work axis
You can also use the mouse to roll here
This is a basic operation of the walk show
And then
Let me see if you have any questions
In the walk show process
Wearing clothes into the pants
The second part will talk about it
Then look at the back
Back on the bag
Can the bag on the back be embroidered in this way
The bag on the back is fine
There will be a waist bag in the third part
If you want to make some cross-body bags
It's okay
It's just that the bag on the back is not very easy to do
Because the bag on the back has to be fixed on the model's hand
But the model's hand is a little bit bigger
well
Can the fabric be calculated
Can you make clothes A, B, C
What does it mean to make clothes A, B, C
Where do you want to put it
Can you be more detailed
There will be a playback
Let's go to the second part
The second part is to show you this
A set of clothes like this
Good for everyone
Open this first
This is the original state of the clothes we normally finish making
Let me go back to the simulation mode first
Then hide this line
It's a set of clothes like this
Let's take a look at this set of clothes
Now there is a shirt inside
This is a jacket jacket
A large jacket jacket
I put it on
Let me hide it and look inside
Inside, there is such a shirt and a pair of pants
You can see this place
Shirts are worn inside the pants
I hide this pair of pants
You can see
In fact, there are a lot of clothes here
In order to facilitate our operation
We can use a new function of 5.2
Called group
Then I will group all three of his clothes
In this way
I can choose these three clothes very conveniently later
I can choose these three clothes
OK
I can choose one of the clothes at once
For example, I can hide this pants directly for him
Someone just asked me
My shirt is twisted like this
What should I do
Usually we are dealing with this
When a relatively complicated set of clothes is paired
If you just want to adjust one piece of clothes
Then fix all the other clothes for him
Otherwise
Imagine
I move three layers
You may fight with each other in three layers later
Then I fixed one or two layers of it
In this way
This layer will be relatively stable
Because the other two layers do not move
Just move
In this way
What about this dress
Think about it
Because he is on the outside
He and this
The clothes inside have an external relationship
So we have to give him a cold freeze on the outside
Right
If you have taken a lesson from Mr. Molly
Will know that this place should be frozen
In this way
He can stay outside steadily
OK
Then let's take a look at this place
For example
Let's take a look
I think this place seems to be a little unstable
Then I want to adjust
Before that
Check my clothes first
Quality
If the particle diameter is too small
My simulation speed is very slow
For example, like here
Here I
This
Because I want to adjust the top
I'll untie him first
OK
Take a look at this part
This part is ten
OK
This place is still
I make him a little smaller
Because he is a
There is a draw
I'll make him a little smaller for the time being
OK
For example, this place
This pants is a little crooked
I want to adjust it for him
Then we can consider
For example, I'll freeze this for him first
Frozen
More frozen
The other two layers do not move
One-to-one simulation of this layer
His simulation speed will be relatively faster
For example, I pull like this
It's a little hard to pull
It doesn't matter
We can use this
Select the grid tool
Find this one
After opening the simulation
Choose this one
Then use this grid tool
To quickly adjust
Pull him to the left a little
OK, let go
This side is also
Pull him over here a little bit
Be careful of the candle
Because there is another layer outside
Although we hide it
But don't forget that he's still there
So when you pull it out
Be careful not to pull it out
Go to his side
I'll switch back to this selection tool
Take a look
He's a little bit to the front
Pull him over here
Adjust his dress
state
This is the pants
If you want to adjust the shirt
Freeze the pants
Then we activate the shirt
Activate
For example, this position
I'm going to adjust the lining of the shirt
I'll hide it first
Take a look at the simulation
There's a little detail about this dress
I don't know if you've noticed
Here
We have three buttons on the outside
But there's another button in the real clothing, right?
Note that the button has a conflict
So before we go to the show
For this button
We need to put this button first
Conflict
We use the editor
Choose a twist tool
After selecting the twist
In the first editor
Turn off his conflict first
Turn it off
After turning it off
He won't conflict with my version
The two of them won't fight each other
So this is very important
Because it will directly affect
When you go to the show
A stable state of the neck
So turn off this conflict
The part in the pants below
Let's not twist
Because he's in there
Anyway, you can't see it
I'm going to delete it
And then I used it
The tool we talked about earlier
Click here
Click on the two points
Just set it up
It still needs to be fixed
Otherwise, later
It's not easy to deal with it when it's open
It may bring some instability
So it's better to fix it
Take a look at your questions
How to hide clothing
Use that choice
Select the move tool
In 3D
When you select this board
Press Shift Q
Hide this
Of course
If you can't remember the shortcut
You just right-click
There will be a hidden 3D board on the right-hand menu
Next to it is his shortcut
Shift Q
If you want to
Look at me
The pants and the jacket are hidden
Right
You can use this tool here
Show it out
Display clothing
Shift W
So his shortcut is Shift W
It can be displayed
I choose it
Shift Q
Hide
Here is also Shift Q
Then let's take a look
I just talked about the position of this door
The buttons inside
Turn off the conflict
Delete
Out of the conflict
Turn off the conflict
The buttons inside
Delete
Change a way to fix it
And then this place
See it
It's actually a little uneven
This kind of opening simulation
You just pull it a little bit
Pay attention
Flat
In its flat state
Don't pull it out
Look at me now
This state
It's wrong
If I show this
You can see it coming out
So here
Be careful
Be careful when handling
Someone just asked
I'll show it out
For example, this state
Didn't someone just ask
My clothes
Rushed out
What to do
Let's see how to deal with it
Actually
It's easy to deal with
Here you can
You can put this
I put
I can't use this board
Let it freeze first
Touched
Freeze
And then?
I'm going to deal with these two boards alone
You need to pay attention to these two boards
It's because there's a lot of fish in it
There's a lot of fish in it
So he ran out
We can use the selected board
There's a function on the front of the mouse
It's called微向缩率
Let's add an 80 to it
That is to say
Let it shrink its tail
Tighten
In this way
Its amount will be shrunk
It will become more attached
And then set it to a level called negative one
If the level is negative one
It will go in
If the level is positive
Then it will go out
Now it's inside
So it's negative one
And then I'll touch you
Wait a minute
I'm here
Set this up together
OK
And the layers of these two boards
The layers of these two boards together
Otherwise it will be affected
A little bit
It's going in
When most of it goes in
Don't continue to simulate
Because sometimes the layers will have some
Bad influence
Because our board
It's its distribution level
When one front meets the other
It can identify whether it is the front or the back
But if it's this place
It's up to you
If it's up to you
It's hard to distinguish the right and the wrong
It will keep fighting
So when most of your layers are OK
After that
Turn off this layer
Simulate again
That's it
This place is a little unstable
Before simulation
Let's activate it
Activate
Simulate together
Because it was frozen just now
It doesn't have that space of movement
So you activate it outside
Let it have a space of movement
Then give it a light pull
Gently pull it out
Be careful to be gentle
You can pause the simulation in the middle
To remember this state
In case it comes out
You can pull it back again
In this way
It's basically flat
It's flat inside
And then
Didn't I set a rate of contraction just now
80 to 90
Slowly put it back
Don't put it all at once
It will rush out
A little bit
What is internal damping
I'll tell you about it later
Let's listen to it patiently
Let me take a look at this place
This place
Because it has a fold
So when we pull it
Be careful
Pull it to the side
Be careful here
Because its fold is here
Gently pull it out
Adjust it appropriately
Give it the amount
Just pull it apart evenly
it is good
First
In this way
We basically
Give it this position
Adjusted it first
Then the stabilizing line of the torque
Also adjusted it for him
Of course, this torque
Can be turned off
Just in case
Then we have to check it
I said before
I have checked the force
Go in, right
Don't be me
A little bigger
And then
Let's check another one
It's called its
Conflict thickness
Because we have explained it before
In order to prevent
The fabric
In the process of dynamic simulation
Rush out of each other
We have to adjust the conflict thickness
A little bigger
Because the layers here
Relatively complicated
You can adjust it to 2.5
Or 3
All right
Just let it
Keep each other
Keep a safe
Conflict space
Including the outer layer
Also
Adjust it a little bigger
All right
After that
Give it a simulation
So it will be a little bit
But in the distance
In fact, it is not so obvious
OK
All right
After that
Let's take a look again
Explain again
Another little trick for doing that
Ah, a little trick for doing the show
Ah, if we do the show
This is a normal clothing structure
Right
But if we do the show
In fact
The total of the show inside
Is not visible
Ah
The more fabric
The greater the calculation
It needs
The longer the show
So
For the unreadable version
You can
Er
Delete it
Because you can't see it
Inside
Then you
Delete a few pieces of cloth
To reduce the computer's calculation
So it can be
Faster
And faster
To do it
Today's example material
Can I
Give you a practice
Um
Let me take a look
Today is a total of
How many
Two or three
Right
Give this
The first one
The first one and the second one
I'll put it out
For you to practice
Ah
Then we go down
The sleeves I just said
Delete
Then in addition
Ah
Another example
If you are
Put that
We put that
Ah
The final suit
Wearing this
Out of the clothes
Then we know that the suit
Is made of cloth
Ah
In this case
If you want to go to the show
It is recommended to delete the cloth
Reduce the layer of clothing
Try to let this
The calculation of the movement of the show
Let it
As simple as possible
Ah
This can avoid a lot of problems
Ok
Then
In this way
The clothes are simplified for him
Ok
Now
If we
Next
Try to go to the show
Let's imagine
What will happen
Ah
First of all
What I can think of
The problem is
This one
He is a door-to-door
Then in the process of walking
He may
Open
Right
And then even slide
It's very similar to the collar
Because he is here
There is no fixed
Ah
There is another problem
Is
My coat is heavier
He will pull my left and right
At that time
Not symmetrical
Because you can see
My left and right are basically symmetrical
At that time
Come here
And then go over here
Then it's crooked
Right
So these things
May exist
As soon as I know
I don't have to try it
I'm going to take it now
Solve this problem for him
Ah
First of all
In order to prevent my shirt from running
Ah
I'll take it
Let me take a look
Let's fix the shirt for him first
Then this version
Hide it for him first
We just need to be in the two positions of the point
Add two to him
Fake needle
Like just now
Fix the version to the virtual model
This one
A needle
Ah
Add two to him
That way
Make sure this position won't move
Move
Ah
And then we'll look at it again
I just talked about a question
Is
My place
Open
He may walk around
The whole clothes on this side will fall
Understand
If you don't understand
I have a picture here
Let me show you
Let's take a look
I saw this one
This picture
Ah
It's like this
Understand
This place will fall
So we need to give it
Find a way to fix it
That for this kind of open door
It has a very useful technique
I'm going to fold it up first
And then I'm going to fix this
I'll just add a doorbell to it
Then I'll just draw a board here
The board doesn't have to be too big
Just a bar
I can hear the sound
Can you tell where the sound is?
I'll add a piece of fabric here
Apply this fabric to this place
Let's look for this piece of cloth
Then we can directly select this piece of cloth in 3D
The quick arrangement function in the upper right corner
Just click on it
Just click on a position again
Put it on
After putting it on
Take a look
I'm probably going to fix it in this position
Then where am I
Where is it
It's in its fold
On the line
So to make it easier to see
Let's change the 2D texture to white
I'm not sure where the powder is here
Right
When my mouse is moving freely on this point
You can see that point in 3D
As a guide
Probably in this position
Then copy to the blue point
Come over
Then here is an approximate position
Don't have to be very precise
To the blue point
Then this is OK
Then this cloth
I'm using a cloth now
default cloth
Let's take a look at its physical properties
In the physical properties
Just choose this cloth
The properties and the details below
You can see the details of your physical properties
You can see its default
Is our 5.2 version of default fabric
Its stretch is
Such a situation
That is to say, it can still stretch
In order to prevent it from being too dirty
We can make this value a little bigger
For example, the tail is adjusted to 40
Then this is a little smaller
It doesn't matter if it's a mirror
Mainly the tail prevents it from pulling too much
40 to 50 is fine
Then for the angle of the corner line
Also set it appropriately
It doesn't matter here
Then its softness
It doesn't matter
Because we don't need to see its
The dynamic process
I'll hide it later
Then simulate
Maybe I'm now
The diameter of the sample is still relatively large
I'll set it up for him
From 1 to 15
In this way
If this cloth stays here
Then you can see
Usually our collar will have one
Such a trend
Right
So if you want its shape to be more natural
You can consider this
Put this
The rectangular panel is adjusted to a 7-line panel
So that its door will be more natural
You see there is a bright one here
How to adjust
Our relatively simple adjustment
Is to use the editor panel tool
Move this point to him
But pay attention
Did I just sew this line and this line?
If I move this point, the length will change
So to make it easier
I'm not going to adjust the sewing line anymore
We can use another tool
Long press the editor panel tool
There is an editor point or line below
Then select this line
You can see that you can rotate this line
Double click this center point
Move it up
You can come around this point
Give him a little turn
This line
Give him a slight 7-line
You can see that one piece is missing here
Then this side is also the same operation
Give him a little turn
This is the same operation
The design is the same
But the line is also a little bit different
If the line is smaller
And it looks like you're going to give him a little bit more
Is the picture of the shoe
Is it a sticker or a template simulation
What is the socks
The socks are stickers
That is, we choose this model
Then after the attracts the data machine
Because of this, it is more convenient to reduce the amount of material.
What is the difference between MD and MD?
Is there anyone to help me answer it?
Because I explained it to you in front of you.
See if everyone understands.
Save the recorded file
If you save the recorded file, you can save the project file later.
I will continue to say
I just adjusted it to a T shape.
Let's simulate it again.
In this way, its shape will be more natural.
Of course, you can also add it a little wider.
I won't add it here.
You can not hide this version now.
Because you can pay attention to whether it is stable or not after walking.
So don't hide it first.
Then there is another problem.
Now fix the door handle
This can ensure that my clothes will not slip down.
But there is another problem.
My clothes now
It can also move, right?
When I walk, maybe this collar will also have a slope on the left and right.
So I'd better put my big jacket on it.
Set the position of the collar so that it doesn't move around.
Here you can consider
Someone just mentioned a friction factor.
Of course you can use
Select this piece of cloth
Click on the sheet and you can see this piece of default fabric.
Select this piece of cloth at the bottom of its physical attribute.
There will be a
Friction factor
It should be a friction factor.
Then here you can adjust it a little bit to prevent the clothes from sliding.
But I personally think this method
In fact, how much do you want to adjust?
This is a test walk to check.
So it's not very effective.
So I personally prefer to add needles directly.
In this case, it's more conscious.
So we still use the needle tool.
Then see this side is not to put it
Not to put the jacket on the model.
This may cause some problems.
Because it penetrates a piece of cloth
It may not be very stable.
So here we use a fake seam.
That is to say, the points on the board and the points on the board are fixed.
Here, for example, I found this position.
Click on it and then I'll click on it around here.
This point is fixed and that's it.
This collar is also a Q hidden.
Then fix this point for him.
OK.
Keep disappears.
How to use online building material should use the expected
news
You use one.
That one, that one.
The article cannot go with the product.
Can a recorded file be a single and synchronized style?
Yes.
After loading the book,
record the file
video.
The video capture here can lead to a walking show video
It's gray now because this file doesn't have a walking show action in it
The model's inner atmosphere is close
You guys are a little mischievous
How do you put it in when you pull it out?
Do you use it on the model or on the fabric?
If it's a model, you just click on the model
You can click on the fabric and add it in
And if it's a fabric, you just click on the fabric
Then you find the fabric in the attribute editor
So it depends on who you are
Just click on the object and then find the tool in the attribute editor
Let's go on here
We just fixed this place
OK
Then SHIFT W, let's show it
All the clothes are displayed
Simulate
You can't see anything like this
Because it's actually a very weak fix
All activated
In this state, I'm going to walk
Come to animation mode
Then let's find an action for it
Just like the previous one
Let's analyze
Find it in the attribute editor
It's an old model model
So we are female V1
The first version is a model before 5.0
Then you can find motion in this
Then this one is also a more complicated clothes
So I still use this simple action
It's just a swing
It doesn't have a waist insertion
It doesn't have any more exaggerated movements
You can take a look
It's still this swing action
Just swing it left and right
Then click record
Then this dress
Because it has more layers
There are more panels
So its calculation is also relatively large
So you can see it now
Even if my particle monitor is set higher
It still takes some time
To finish the whole process
So here
We're not going all the way
I'll show you later
It's set up
What kind of state it's going to be
Then it ends here
I seem to be a little tired
Wait a minute
Okay, delete it here
Delete it here
Okay, reply back
Then we may have some
People will be more curious
Some of them are more curious
How to add a stage to this walk show
Let me introduce you to that
Some of the stages that Kolo brought
How to use
Then wait a minute
The third part will introduce you
How to create your own stage
First of all, in the library
There will be a stage folder
Can be found here
Then we double-click
You can see inside
In 5.2
There will be some
Provided this
Pre-set stage
If you want to use it
Pay attention to what format it is
It's a DPRJ
It's a project file
So you have to record it
Add this project file before the walk show animation
Otherwise, if you assume
Suppose you're done recording
All done
You add it again
Your action will disappear
So this is
This is a small problem
Everyone should pay attention
Here, for example, I use this
Stage 3
You can see this preview on the mouse wheel
Then right-click to add to the work area
You can also double-click and left-click
If you double-click and left-click
It will open by default
Remember to switch to increase at this time
OK
Click to confirm
0 0 0
Old model
Yeah, it's an old model
There was a question just now
The action of Mixamo
Can't be used
Chloe model can't wear
OK
You put Chloe's model
FBX first
Or VJ can
You can choose to use FBX here
Of course, you can try both
These two formats can be
Then pay attention to the preservation
Put the texture picture together
Save out
Then you upload it to Mixamo
On top
Go to an action network
Then download another FBX
Enter Chloe
You can use it
Very simple
You can go to the official website
We have a forum
There is an article in it
To introduce this process
Check the draw
Wait a minute
Let's take a look at the time
Because I feel
There is still a lot of live content today
I remember
If I have time to tell you
OK
Draw
Just the third style
There are wrinkles
Wait a minute
Take a look
Yes, the white one needs to be transparent
I haven't dealt with it yet
Wait a minute
Why don't you deal with it now
Because if you hide it
What if he and the clothes inside
Conflict is not stable
I won't find it in time
So before recording the action
I won't put it transparent first
Because I still want to see it
Wait until it's all gone
I'll take this fabric
Let's zoom in and take a look
I pressed a focus on the F key
Let's set the transparency of this fabric
Set it back
You can't see it
So don't worry
Because the setting of this transparency
Will not change your embroidery movement
Will not let your embroidery movement disappear
So slow down
No problem
Let's go down
In this way
The action of the stage comes in
After that
There is a grid on the ground
We are at the 3D window
There is an environment element display hidden
Hide this grid for him
So you can see this stage
Then came the animation mode
At this time
I'm taking this stage
To record the embroidery
Pay attention to the stage of the cloth
Use it like this
Then you click to start recording
Then he finished recording
It's ok
What about the time here
I won't record it
I recorded it in advance here
Just press this setting
Record this action directly for him
Let's take a look directly
A state after recording
There is a video here
I can show you
This is what I put
The process of his walk
Recording process
Record this process
I recorded it
You can see
After setting up
His action is lagging
Because he is recording
Then after setting up
You can see that the whole process is still relatively stable
Let's take a look at that
How to turn off this video
How to turn off
Wait a minute
it is good
I'll just open it
Recorded
This is already recorded
Wait a minute
Work
Ok
How to download
I just look at the screen
Look at this
Here
There is a process
Okay
I will
here
I am
No
So
You can see
This is already
No
It should be
Here
I see
There is one
Come on
Go
This will make it look a little bit better
That's it
You can see that it's very stable on it
It won't fall off
So if you want to record this kind of style in the future
This kind of left-handed embroidery
You can do this
If you solve it for a long time, will there be a problem with the difference
Can you explain the so-called difference in detail?
I don't really understand this question
How to save recorded videos
There are two ways
One is that you directly put this picture
Record it into a video
In this case, it means that it has no lighting rendering
That's in the file
Video capture video
Because I already have this left-handed movement
You can see that this video is on
Then you click on the video
It's recorded here
You can automatically generate a video
This is a normal video
It's very fast
The other one is rendering a left-handed video in rendering
This will take a lot of time
Wait a minute, we will introduce the third part
How to operate this part
Ok, this is the second part
It's this style
Is there any problem with this style?
If there is no problem, we will enter the third part
How to rotate the angle when recording
You can choose like this
But it's actually not very natural
Because you don't want that kind of dynamic camera effect
That kind of thing is not easy to do
Maybe you need to cooperate with some other 3D software
For example, something like Zenimax or Maya
You add some dynamic cameras to do
The clothes stop at the top
Clothes stop at the top
The character is at the bottom
No
Anyway, I haven't encountered such a problem so far
In general, there will be no such problem during the recording process
I know, I know
The difference is that the clothes stop at the top and the character is at the bottom
If you
Normally, you shouldn't encounter such a problem
Take a look at which version you are using
Will that
Is there any problem?
Isn't Blender fragrant?
Blender is also fragrant
Blender is free, of course it's fragrant
If you can use anything, it's good
I don't know, this is all slow motion
Yes, it's not called a walk show at the beginning
At the beginning, we are going to do a recording first
I explained the recording process at the beginning
Maybe at that time, some of our classmates haven't arrived yet
What about recording?
It is the action of opening the model
The model drives the clothes to move
The whole process of moving clothes will be calculated by the system and recorded
This is a recording process
So it takes a long time
Because the clothes need to be simulated first
After that, it can be played
How can it be recorded to the effect you are playing now?
I
Just follow the steps I just mentioned
To make a adjustment
Then click to record
After recording, this is the effect now
I didn't go through any processing here
It's like this in the software
OK, then we go down to the third part
To pause
To the simulation mode
Let's talk about the third part
The third part
The third part first
Let's take a look at this
I can't see it
Basically, we will make such a set of effects
First of all, I will open this initial document first
The initial document is one of them
There is only a state of clothing and bags
What kind of playback format is preserved in the recorded left show for the customer to see
If you use the recording function of that cloud
If you record it, it's all in AVR format
Then you look at the player on your customer's side
Can you use AVR to play
If not, you can use that kind of video editing software
Or this kind of software to transfer code
To put that one
This EDI is converted to MP4
That way, it might be better to play some
OK, this kind of clothes
This kind of clothes
Let's take a look at the first step
For example, this place is now set to 8
It's okay
For the time being
Because of this clothes
I don't really deal with it
We mainly deal with its accessories
Then let's take a look at this bag
This bag
Let's talk about it first
If your bag is to be made
What kind of settings should be made
Then I won't teach you here
How to put the bag on this clothes
Because I'm worried about this
The course time will be too long
When this bag is done
We are going to walk
Need to first confirm
Do you have the physical properties of your bag set
Because we know that the bag is like this leather bag
It's harder
So let's take a look at this fabric
What kind of settings did I do to it
First of all, it's one
I used our cloud default one
A default trim for green leather
This default leather attribute
Then I have some adjustments to its bending strength
Make it bigger
It will be relatively hard to stop after it is enlarged
Can be maintained in such a form
Then take a look at the details inside
I hide the model shift a
How to look at the model here
There is a display hidden in the model
Model shift a
Then put this clothes
Clothes
I also have a group here in advance
Shift q hidden
Let's take a look at this bag
My approach to this bag is to add two strips to it
Then I put on a belt in the middle
Is such a structure
In the process of walking
Because it will move
There are two possibilities
One possibility is that the shape of this bag will change
Because it is still cloth after all
It may not be able to maintain such a hard weight
Then for the first question
We can choose this bag
What operation do you do
Right click
You can see that there is a shape change in the 3D right click
In this way, you can put this
The shape of these panels is fixed
Then it will be deformed
It won't change a lot
It may change a little
It won't affect too much
Then what is the second problem
Because I didn't fix it in the middle
So in the process of walking
We know that the model will have one
When you walk
It will have a habit when you lift your foot
Then in this process
It is very likely that this bag will move
This is the top of the powder
The bottom is the powder
Then in this way
In the process of rushing
It may rush out of this bag
If it rushes out, the bag will fall down
This is a problem I found in the process of experiment
How to deal with this problem
In fact, it is used with the same tool as just now
I also used a fake powder tool here
Look at this side
How can this side be fixed
I will fix this side with my belt
It will definitely not fall
This should be easy to understand
In order to find a position
You can see that it is inconvenient for me to add it like this
Because you see
If you add it like this
It is very likely that it will be bent
These two points are not vertical
Because our vision is not aimed at it
I withdraw
How to add
There is a little trick
We are in 3D
In the form of the display of this clothing board
There is one called semi-transparent
There is one called semi-transparent in the physical display
Then when I click on the mouse
You see my 2D board
My 2D here
Pay attention
This blue dot will follow
Just there
For example, I click
There is a index here
Then I can't click on the back
Because my round board is in front
It doesn't matter if you can't click on the back
Just find its position in the 2D
See around here
Come a little more
Here
Clean it up
The next one is also
Because my round board is on
So I don't have to go to the 2D point anymore
I can click on the round board at the 3D point
Then come here directly
Click again
You can add a few more to prevent it
Fall down
Click again
Here is
Add four to each of them
This can ensure that it is
It will definitely not fall
There will be no rotation
This kind of awkward problem
Well, these points are added
After that
Let's take a look
I'll show you all of them
Let's take a look at the surface of a peony
This position
It's just a little bit of a gap
If we just set it now
It's too dead
Is it unnatural?
Then we can put this
The value of the pin is selected
In the mouse machine
You can set the length of the pin
I set it 1 to 2mm here
For example, I set 2mm
That way it will ensure that there is a gap of 2mm between the points
So it won't be too dead
Bag connection
Bag
This bag should be easy to do
Ping-pong ball, can't you put it in?
The gold line is lazy.
We have taught Mr. Mori before in class.
You can take a look at a playback of the previous live broadcast.
Put it back again.
I'll show you a little bit.
This is my waist bag.
This is my bag.
Now the simulation speed is relatively slow.
Because I have a lot of panels, it's lagging.
So the same.
In order to make my simulation speed faster,
a very important tool is to freeze the panels that don't need to be simulated.
Freeze.
It must be frozen here.
Because there are layers.
Then simulate again.
This will make the simulation speed faster.
Then let's talk about the ring buckle in the middle.
Wait a minute.
The ring buckle is also to be simulated.
If you want to put some solid metal buckles or some hard plastic things on your clothes to follow the simulation,
you need to pay attention to one point.
Don't import it as a virtual model.
What does that mean?
Let me explain it to you.
I'll delete it first.
In other words, we need to make it move along with your clothes.
This is called a copy.
In the form of a copy.
Because the copy can be glued to the panel and move along with the clothes.
But what you need to know is that our copy has no conflict.
That means it will penetrate with our panel.
Very stable.
Because it doesn't have a layer of simulation there.
So at this time, how do we deal with it?
You can see here.
How did I do it?
I made one more panel here.
Fold it back first.
This is a very normal structure.
Then I made a small panel for it in the middle.
I hid this panel.
I'll show it to him.
I use this panel to connect this belt.
To fix this belt.
Of course, you don't need it later.
Just hide a part of it first.
Leave a little bit.
And then for this place.
Maybe we usually use this folding tool, right?
We use the folding tool to give him this panel.
Find this line and fold it back.
At this time.
The angle of the fold will be randomly set to 0 or 30 degrees or how many degrees.
It's the number of degrees you fold.
If you open the simulation at this time and try it.
You will see that this place is very sharp and flat.
At this time.
If you put your ring in.
It can't hide in this hole very well.
It can't just hide in this hole.
Then there will be a problem.
It will come out.
So here.
We're going to give him this line.
Handle to 180 degrees.
Let it be flat.
Then the folding intensity is randomly set to 5.
Adjust it to 20.
Keep it under this intensity of 180 degrees.
Under the angle.
The mouth is flat.
Then it can be formed into two holes.
Then let's put this ring in.
For example.
Here.
Here I have a ring.
What about this ring?
The solid component.
We usually randomly set it to OBJ.
It's OBJ.
That is to say.
Even if you made a ring with a plate in the shell.
That's also a file.
First, I'm going to turn this ring into OBJ.
I'm not going to hide this process.
What about the OBJ file?
Add it directly to the working area by right-clicking.
Next.
This window is very important.
Remember to choose to increase.
Then be sure to remember to choose to import as a copy.
Don't choose to read virtual models.
If it's a virtual model.
It can't follow your outfit.
So this is very important.
And then it's not adding clothes.
It's not what it's not.
It's just a copy.
This point.
Draw the focus.
Everyone has to write a note.
This has to be written down.
This is a heavy middle.
Good.
Go down.
The proportion here.
I'm on the good side.
The default position is 0 0 0.
That's it.
Click on the bottom to the ground.
No need to confirm.
This is how you import it into this default position.
You can see.
Because I'm in this position.
It automatically appears here.
When it's imported with a copy.
There will be two icons in the upper right corner.
One is for it.
A shrink adjustment.
You can see it shrink adjustment.
A little bit smaller.
And then click again.
Turn off this shrink function.
And then the upper right corner.
The other one is called sticky.
Watering tool.
You can.
The right foot is drooping again.
It's drooping.
Watering tool.
Put it in the middle of this little board.
It's a little bit more stable.
Because in the middle.
Its movement trajectory.
Compared to the two sides.
It's more even.
If you set it here.
If it moves a little bit here.
Your ring might move a lot of distance.
Understand?
Try your ring.
Fixed on it.
It's in the center of this movement.
After you get to this point.
Let me show you.
What functions does the watering tool have?
The watering tool.
Let me show you.
And then fix it.
I'm not going to use glue to pinch it.
And then?
Open the simulation.
Then gently pull it out.
Can you see it?
It can follow your board.
For simulation.
Okay.
Turn it off.
At this point.
No need to pinch it again.
Click the positioning ball.
Adjust the position of the ring.
Just a little bit.
Oh, I'm going to turn it again.
It's on.
Okay, there's a little bit of a line down there. Come down a little bit more
Oh, that's it. Basically, you can't really see it like this
Then click on this ring and you can set its material to a metal
So this is a metal ring
I didn't set it to zero just now
Set its transparency to zero
So this structure is done
Okay, that's it. My belt is over
So the belt gives it a direct right click
Move it for him
Move it
Okay, this is my belt part
Take a break and look at everyone's questions
Then continue to drink
The color of the zipper is light and the other colors are not three-dimensional enough
What about this question?
I suggest you don't scan black
There are pure white
These two colors are actually
Its color is reflected in the text
It's easy to say that it's either too dark or too dark
So I suggest you try to choose the normal color
Just don't be too bright or too dark
The color of the sample
The bottle is water-based
Yes
The model is tied to the three-model action
And then lead to no text
This classmate
Note that when you lead the model out of the club
When the model leads to OBJ
The option to keep the text together
Must be linked
The text must be kept together
It's not three-dimensional to add a sticker to the chain
Then I suggest you can do this
Which chain do you use
You scan the real color of the sample
Apply it to an application
Apply a hair line sticker
What's even on the application
Don't we have a hair line sticker?
There's something else
It can also be used as a calligraphy
And it's a highlight
You use all of these
Then its effect will be very positive
But like that calligraphy
And highlight
This highlight
It usually has a better effect when it's bleached
Let's go down
This is a belt
And then we're going to give him a head
For example
For example, I want to give him a head scarf
Or a hat
We are targeting these two categories
There may be different processing methods
Let me tell you about this hat first
I put this hat in first
Let's take a look at the structure of this hat
Then analyze how to tie it to the model
For a walk show
This hat came in
Then see if you are wearing a hat
This hairstyle is not suitable
You just need to use a suitable hairstyle
What about wearing a hat
Either delete the model's hair
You can choose it as it is
You can delete it with the right button
Or you just change its hairstyle
For example, if you want to wear a hat
Usually you may use a short hair
This short hair
Switch it
Take a look
It will be more suitable to use a short hair
For example, this
Or this
The short hair will be more suitable
Then take a look again
The version of this hat
It is relatively complicated
Because it has a face
You can see it has a face
Then it still has a face
There is also a inside
Inside and face
Have
The structure is more complicated
At this time
If you let him follow the model
If you walk together
Not realistic
Just
You let him walk in the form of fabric
Then it's hard
It's hard to stabilize
So for this kind of complicated style
I suggest you put this hat
Give him a file
Pour out
OBJ selected
Pour it out
Pour out an OBJ
Then delete it first
Wait a minute
I have a ready-made hat on my side
For example, there is a hat here
3D file
There is also a butterfly knot here
Take it away
This is an OBJ file
It is wrapped in text
So it's that ZIP format
Increase the insert as a copy
Note that it is still a copy
Then click OK
If you want your hat to move with the model
That's actually very simple
You find a way to put this hat
Stick to the top of your model's head
So how does your model move?
He can follow your model to move
Understand?
For example
For example, I give him
This model
Give him a new hairstyle
It was just a
This hairstyle
There are so many hairstyles
There are all in the cloud
Because I use 5.2
We have a lot of 5.2
A lot of useful resources are added
Then the hair will be there
Now it is an OBJ
Note that it is an OBJ
So you can see that there is a glue team
But I want to put it
Where to stick
There is an object to stick
So
How to do it
We can do this
In this 2D
Draw the top of the head
Draw a very small board
Then I just want to let this board
Stuck to the model
It's okay
it is good
I'll give him this hat first
Move up a little
Then let's look at this
Still use this quick arrangement
Put it here
On the top
After putting it
What to wear
No problem
It doesn't matter
Come up a little
it is good
Then give him a
Fixing needle
Add a fixing needle to the whole board
Then
Right click on the fixing needle
There is a function called
Fix the fixing needle to the model
Then you can't see it
Can't see it
It's actually fixed
You can see this position below
After that
You put this hat
Isn't it a
Adhesive?
Use glue
Put it
Glue it to this
I may not be able to see this hair
I put this hair
Let me take a look
I set this one
Model
I can't see it
I can see it like this
I can't choose it
It's okay
It doesn't matter
Let's do this first
Let's just take it off
See if you can touch it
No
Then we'll give it to him first
Then fix this board again
Stick it to this position first
His position is wrong, right?
Don't care about him
I'll turn it later
I'll adjust his position later
Let's do this
I'll turn it a little bit
Otherwise I can't see that board
Then I put this board
Fixed to the virtual model
Fixed
After fixing
Next I just need to adjust
The position of this hat
Adjust the position of the hat
Let him adjust
Let him wear it
But when you adjust
You have to be careful
Don't let your hat
Through the model's hair
You probably wear
I'll probably wear it here
Of course you can adjust it more accurately
In this way
You wait
In the process of walking
This hat will follow you
The model went
For example, I'm here
Go to animation mode
For example
For example, I'll give him a little walk
A little walk
Not much
Then go to that
Motion
V2
I want him to walk faster
I'll make this a little bigger
Although he will be ugly
But let him speed up a little bit more
Okay, let's go to the simulation mode
Below
Under the animation mode
Suppose I give him a walk now
Then his current speed will be very slow
Because he's in this place
There will be more things
You can see it
This hat is moving
I won't record it
Then his position will not move
Because we have already put the whole
The board is firmly fixed on the model's head
So this hat won't move
He won't have a position of bias
Then I won't continue here
This is a hat
There are many layers
Delete it
There is another one
That's what I just talked about
That head
What if it's a head
Then the head is a hat
I'll add it back to the costume
I'll multiply it
I'll appreciate it
I'm going back to the same place
I didn't choose the right position just now
It's zero
Oh
First put this model back to it
Move the models to the center
Then I'll add it in
And apply
I'm not sure if I'm doing it right or wrong
The compression is a bit...
I feel a bit uncomfortable with two hairs here
Okay
I'll apply the hairspray here
And this hairspray
I didn't use this hairstyle when I was doing the hairspray
I used this hairstyle
This hairstyle
Of course, you can adjust its position a little bit more
This is a hairspray
The structure of this hairspray is relatively simple
In fact, how to operate
You can use a bag to operate it in a similar way
You give it a hairspray
Format it
I have already shaped it
You can shape it first
Make sure it doesn't have too much deformation
Then you use this
Fix it to your model
On the head, on the body
You set it up one by one
Just add a lot of points
But I suggest that you don't just add it along one side
Just set it up
Then set it down
Then set it up
After setting it up like this
It won't have too much deformation
It can be settled on the top of the head
Follow the model in the form of fabric
Go for a walk
I won't operate it because of the time relationship here
Because it's not complicated here
Okay
Of course, in fact, for the simplest structure
If you want simple operations
You can also turn it into OBJ
Then do the same operation on it
Pinch it to this board
It can also follow the model
These two methods are fine
Okay, this is the head and hat of the head
It's related to this kind of configuration on the head
One operation method
Next, let's talk about earrings
Do you have any questions?
Is there any way to prevent too much conflict in advance?
Is your so-called conflict too big?
Do you mean that the clothing will not be stable?
Or what?
Is the size of the earring very small or is it a conflict?
For example, the border of the wallet
That is to say
In fact, I will introduce it to everyone in advance
That is, we have to do some editing on the clothing before the walk
There is a core idea
That is to simplify some of the engineering details of your walk style
Then you look like a very narrow one
A very narrow one
What's that called?
If you say you made a round bucket
Or it's really folded
The kind of bag that goes up
I suggest you delete it
How do you do it after deleting it?
You go with a very narrow one
A very narrow one like this
A very narrow one
A narrow strip
Then put the side of this strip
On the position of your bag
Then increase its conflict thickness
In this case, it is equivalent to making a fake bag
This is to reduce its level
To simplify its operation
Bag
There is a person here who says that the bag can also be obj
What kind of bag to start with?
Bag
If the size of my bag is obj
Maybe it's okay
Because it's not very big
If your bag is bigger
I have explained before
If obj is attached
It will penetrate the plate
What will happen then?
Your bag may be like this
Your bag will be like this
It's not natural
So you still have to come according to your style
Someone is peeking next to you
Yeah
Our little C-jun is peeking
Hahaha
Then I go down
Let's take a look at the earring method
Then I will put this side
Give him a piece of paper that doesn't need it
I'm not using the freezer now
Not using the freezer
Use the reverse
I'm not using the reverse
I'm using the reverse
Because my earring and my other position
There is no level conflict
So I'll give him a reverse
Because he doesn't have a level calculation
Will be faster
Including my waist
Reverse
In this case, my speed will be very fast
Then let's deal with this earring
The core idea of ​​the earring is the same as our hat and this ring
I also fixed this obj to one of my plates
In fact, everyone should already be able to think of
That's actually on my ear
To create a small plate
What about this plate
You can make one
If it's a earring
You can put it all on your ear
Let him not move
But if it's an earring
Because consider our earrings
In the process of walking with people
He will have a floating one
So long earrings
He can make this kind of
Half fixed
Half is a floating plate
This kind of plate
Now, if I want him to move half
Half floating
I definitely need to lower the particle diameter a little bit
Why
You can see that there is no point in the middle
I can't just fix it in half
So I'll lower the particle diameter a little bit
Do you want to know
What happened last time
The impression is too deep
Let's fix the top half
Let's fix it a little less
Fix it here
Then fix the fixing pin to the virtual model body
Fix it
Then we give him this control
Double copy to the other side
Then this side is also
Take it away first
Then you have to set it again
Give him a little adjustment
Here he may find the position
Not too high
It's not too high
Don't touch it
But not too high
Always put it in first
Not at all
And we should be able to fix it
Really
Let's fix it
Let's make it be
like this
Then we just have to worry a little bit
Like this
No
May be
like this
Not really
Like this
We just do it
No
Of course
In fact
One.
Hey
Let me really
Hold on
I said
Then I did this
Leave it
Then
然后呢我们再看到那个耳环把我的耳环导进来
然后我的耳环在这个里面
那同样的耳环也注意是增加导入为附件啊很重要
毫米啊这边确定
机眼又开始了吗
其实我觉得凤眼凤眼我觉得凤眼比较搞笑
接着啊然后用这个胶水把它定到哪里啊
就有刚可能
操作太快了
用胶水不要定到红色的固定死的区域啊
定到它的白色的区域就是它可以移动的区域
但是你不要太底下
因为底下的摆幅太大了
所以要接近红色的点但是呢不要在点上就接近在中间这个位置上啊
放好放好之后呢你就对它进行一个
调整它的位置就可以了
放过来调整一下
这样子穿好
多个角度看一下确保你的耳环是自然的啊好这样放好之后呢你这个杆子呢我就给它设定一个
metal
金属的然后下面这个呢比如说我想给它设定一个珍珠的那我们就可以用这个 silk
或者如果等一下你们是想走渲染的呢那这里有些材质比如说钻石啊玻璃啊这些呢就是要在渲染的状态下可以看到啊那我这里还是用这个
这个
丝绸的吧因为我觉得这个比较贵气啊
然后呢你把这个耳环因为附件呢在客户里面是可以直接肯出 c 复制肯出并连贴然后直接到这个点上单击左键
把它复制过来然后移动旋转位置调一下就OK了啊那我这边就不操作了不操作了那这样的话我整套就给它
该家的配件都加完了然后呢回到我的那个文件啊我直接把这个文件
啊我直接把这个文件
就是我已经调整好的文件给他导入进来可以看一下最终就是这样子调整完就会得到这个状态啊
嗯
In the third part, we will also introduce you to how to import some custom platforms.
The custom platform I introduced here is mainly to see how to create a walking show platform in the cloud software.
In addition, you can also create platforms in other 3D software such as Blender or Zendimax.
After creating, just import it in the form of OBJ.
If you are using a custom platform, it is not necessary to import your platform into it before recording the walking show animation.
You can record it directly, and then import the platform into it.
Then import the same action as before, and then start recording.
This is also a matter of time.
I will show you what kind of effect it can record after setting it up like this.
This is a name.
Just wait a minute.
What is it called?
Increase later, open later.
I opened the project I finished.
I opened the solution.
I'm going to add a new material.
Aside from the new item, you need to try and add an additional one.
Like for example, as I just added a head Christmas head, then I added earrings, right?
When you add these things, it only adds the new thing.
Because you open it, you will clear out the original thing and open a new one.
Then add things will keep your old one, and then add something.
This should be easier to understand.
Metal people makes women look beautiful, and they look than beautiful.
This is a pair of hands
Let's see the animation of this model
This is finished
I will switch this needle part to real time to take a look
It's like this
I still take this transformation action
You can see that after this is finished
It's like this
The needle above is more beautiful
We can hide this fixed needle
We used the default material to make the plate
So you can also set the transparency to 0
In this case, you can't see it at all
Let's play it again
You can see that the earrings will also float
And it's still a little bit of a habit
Then let's see how the stage is realized
Back to the simulation
This one
In this state
I will show you a stage
What about this stage?
Let me show you the project file of this vprj
Because I opened it directly
Take a look at this project file
Because even if I click on the addition
The action will disappear
Because I added a project file
Then the model will not be seen
I will play it for you
This one is the model of the VPR
The model of VPR is the model of the VPR
I made this VPR
You can see this
This is the VPR
The model is the model of the VPR
You can see it
So I'm going to add it to the VPR
You can see that the VPR is made of VPR
So it's not difficult
No difficulties
You just need to determine the size
You just have to follow the movement
It's a little hard to go to the bathroom with a platform
Then let's take a look at that
Then at this time you have to test the platform
In what position
Then how to determine its length
Then at this time you have to pour in a motion first
For example, I just pour in an action
Okay, then at this time to pull your model
You can see
My project file has been moved
Because my project file is a board
Under default
It should be in the middle
Do you understand
It should be in this position
Animation
So you first pour an empty model
Don't draw a board first
After the empty model is poured in
When you start walking
It will return to a starting position, right?
Then you pull it closer
You can see
It's going from here
Right?
Okay, then you are in
Go to the simulation
To adjust the position of your platform
Make sure that your platform
Is able to let this model
Go in the middle of the platform
After you have created it
Then walk again
My computer is starting to get a little tired
Walk back again
Including when you go to set its level
Also ensure that its model
Can be hidden behind that
Just like this
To make this size
This one
Determined
How to determine the height and width
It depends on you
How do you want to take pictures
When you take a picture in the background
For example
You take a picture from this angle
Make sure you are in the process of shooting
Is able to
That is to say
See the entire background
Just
Take an example
I put this
I put the background
Give it for example
This white
In this state
If you want to take a shot
You just
I suggest not to take the white side above
Because it won't look good
Or you can make the background a little bigger
What about the corresponding
Give it some text
You can use this platform
To build a simplified platform
Okay
After that
You put this platform
Select the file
OBJ selected
Then
For example
On the desktop
Give it a name
Note that this is a default setting
If you want to
If you want to adjust the texture later
You can choose multiple targets
Because you can adjust the texture separately
Thick
Millimetre
Then you need to be very important
Is to hook this up
With the texture file
Keep it together
Just pour it out
Okay
This is the production of a platform
After the production
How do we put this platform
I've done it
In such a project file
Let me show you
Then I open it again
The one I just did
A file of a show movement
This is the door of the cloud
Yes
It's my design
Cloud door
This project file
In some cases
Just now
I'm not
Put that project file
Out of an OBJ
And then bring it to the picture
That's what it is
Then it's a VIP
This is the package of the home
File
Directly put this platform
Pour in
When you pour in
Choose
Note
You can choose to open
Increase
All right
Because of the following
Is
Choose to read the scene props
Because you don't have any here
Scene props
So you don't care
Choose to open or increase
All right
He won't give you any other information
Cover it
But
During the insurance
Everyone can
If you feel
If it's too difficult
You just choose to increase it
All right
Increase
Note
Choose to read the scene props
If it's your model
Your model is gone
Your this
Information will be lost
The following
These above are all wrong
Because you are a platform
So it must be a scene prop
Note
The last one
Focus on drawing
It's time to write a note
Read the scene props
All right
Click to confirm
How do you stand up the tree bridge
It's just a positional ball
Let him stand up
It's just you
When you click on a certain object
Isn't there a positional ball?
You come to the side
Use this to give him
Just press four
Come to the side
Use this positional ball
Just stand it up
If you worry
Your positional ball is not accurate
You can right-click on the background
There is a coordinate
Now we are using a screen coordinate
Your axis is not accurate
You can switch it to a world coordinate
In this way
Your coordinate axis
Will not follow your lens
Change to change
To change
You can get a more accurate one
Leadership control
You see that he is the policy
Go for a transition
In this way
You see the scene props
He has arrived in this way
And I came to that animation
Immediately
This one
I can click play right away
Then I turn on the red light
In terms of time, this fabric has a larger particle diameter, so it's still rough when you see this fold, so if you want to make it high quality, you can continue to reduce the particle diameter to 5, and then record it again, and the effect will be very good.
In this way, this is the content of the whole table tennis show, and after that, in the end, I have already said that if you want to show the video, it is very simple, one is the main menu, and I will not say more, I have just demonstrated it, and there is another one, which is to show the video, and at this time, you can find the show on the main menu,
and then you can find the show and open it,
and then in the show,
you can find this picture video attribute,
and after opening this one, there will be such a option on the right side of the video, picture or video, and you can choose animation here,
and after that, you can choose whether the color is right below, and whether you want to save the video, and remember to hook up the video here,
and the frame rate, then use the default 30 frames, because in general, the frames in our cloud system are all 30 frames,
and just hook it up here,
picture size,
because we know that the frame rate is 30 frames,
so when you use the frame rate, it will be a single picture, a single video,
so you only want to make a picture that is how big,
which determines the clarity of your final video,
you can do a little bigger,
but of course you do the bigger,
and the more time you need to spend on the frame rate,
and then the direction is horizontal or vertical,
that is, your final output of the video is horizontal or vertical,
this is a very good understanding,
and then you can make a adjustment below,
We use 1920x1080 a lot because this is in line with the resolution of our screen, and then the following words can be a setting for the background color, and then a saving path is set, which is a basic setting situation.
As for rendering, there are many other ways to use it, but it takes a lot of time to explain this, so you can look forward to our next live stream about rendering.
Today's time is limited, so I won't introduce this part.
After setting up this side, you can click on this refresh to preview.
After previewing, OK, no problem. After determining the angle of the video, just click on the final rendering, and it will automatically give you a rendering.
You can see that the frame rate is 30 frames per second, for example, 30 pictures per second.
How many seconds do you usually need for this walkthrough? You can take a look, it has a time of more than ten seconds.
This means that you will eventually have hundreds of rendering images, which takes a lot of time to render.
At this time, I would recommend that you either do it at night without the computer, and let the computer render it by itself.
This will be a little better, so if you want to render the video, it is reasonable to arrange the time.
This is the content of today's live broadcast.
In the end, you can give everyone a look at one thing.
In the end, we can do this.
What kind of effect can the video rendered in Clue render?
There is a visual video here.
You can see that the material of the fabric, the lighting, and its clarity are much better than that of the default video.
So the effect of the costume will also be more impressive.
So if you are interested in it, you can try it yourself.
All right.
This is all the content I want to introduce to you today.
Do you have any other questions?
We can talk for a while.
Let's see.
It's 9.40 now.
Is it possible to choose an APC when rendering?
Is there any problem?
It is possible.
For example, that the
model is our clothes.
How do you set up a show with multiple sets of clothes?
This, you need to finish it one by one in CLO
After doing it, there are two ways
One is to make the background of CLO white
Then you use the video editing software to remove the background
Then put these one set of clothes in the video
Give it a balance
There is another way
After you finish this one set
Take out the action separately
Go to another 3D software and do a balance
That is, it must be completed by using the external software
How do you use CLO to draw the configuration OBJ file?
Configuration, configuration OBJ
Which configuration are you referring to?
I talked about a lot of configurations today
Which configuration?
Are you talking about this?
This is called BOOST
The COD will look like this
The COD size is about 3 quart
But there are some dimensions of COD
There are some dimensions and the size
This is the last one
After you finish this one set
Go to another 3D software
To make a real CLO
Next, I will show you how to make the CLO
Let's see
MIX
Oh, I forgot to turn on the TV
Let me turn on the TV
Okay, I forgot to turn on the TV
It's fine, it's fine, it's not very big
Then after changing the circle, just add an internal cable to it
Just see how wide you want this circle to be
For example, let's say 3mm
Then convert it to a hole, convert this internal circle to a hole
Now there will be some grid
You make the internal cable smaller
Oops, it's crooked, it's a bit fast
In this way, the circle will come out
But it doesn't have a thickness, right?
Make it a little bigger
Then it will be round
Let's apply this to it
Add another one
Then this circle is done
You just need to export this file to OBJ
It will become an OBJ circle
This is what I just used
This is very easy
Very simple
The socks are for the legs
Yes, it's for the legs
The silk socks at the beginning
Added a color to the legs
After increasing the model
Can you still move after determining the position of the model?
Can move
Open the model's joint point
Let you point to its core
This purple dot
Then you can move it with this locator
You can use this bone to move the whole model
Yes, it's quite fun to do some of the tablecloth
Because I think it's more tiring to do food
It's easier to do in the basket
How to change earrings?
Earring
Let me explain to you
The earrings are just a ring made of board
That's the ring
Make a long strip for it
Or
I seem to have made a circle
Yes, made a circle
Set the hands a little harder
Then add a close stitch
Close stitch
A shape is made
And then a slightly raised
This is also a long strip of board
Set a little harder
Set the line inside
Is here
It's a long strip. There's a cut here.
Then it's going to be a circle.
And then I'm going to give him a 3D diamond.
There's no way to do this with a board.
It's not that there's no way.
The board can be round, but it can't make this kind of cold corner.
So you can use some small 3D accessories to match the board to make some settings.
After the whole thing is done, it's all selected.
And then it's done in the file.
Let's talk about the fur toy.
The fur toy can be painted by itself.
Our topic today is about the show.
If you have this idea, let's see if we have a chance to introduce it to you later.
If you have any live broadcasts you want to see later, you can leave a message on the back of our WeChat public number.
Then we'll plan it after we see it.
Thank you.
Thank you for your support.
One-on-one, one-on-one, one-on-one live broadcast.
If we want to see it.
If you have more friends who play with dolls.
Welcome in, the door is not closed.
The door has always been open.
If OBJ is wrong, it shows X axis, what, what, what.
Well, you can.
If you make a mistake when you import OBJ.
When we import OBJ.
He has a window.
Let me show you.
For example, when I import OBJ.
He's going to have a axis here.
If you're him.
It tells you which axis is wrong.
You switch the axis with him.
Maybe you're in another 3D software.
When you import this OBJ.
It's a vertical axis.
The axis of space is different.
It's a vertical axis in the cloud.
Maybe there's a space.
Other software may be vertical.
It's possible.
So you can check this point.
It's hard to talk about it today.
I hope to talk about it again.
It's okay.
We have that live broadcast.
There's a live broadcast.
Okay, if you don't have any questions.
That's all we have for today's live broadcast.
Thank you, everyone.
Please leave a lot of messages on WeChat.
Have a good night's rest.
Have a pleasant weekend.
Bye bye.
The anchor is down.